<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
  <rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
      <title><![CDATA[Archie Judd]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[Archie Judd - Archie Judd's personal website]]></description>
      <link>https://archiejudd.com</link>
      <image>
        <url>https://archiejudd.com/assets/icons/rss-144x144.png</url>
        <title><![CDATA[Archie Judd]]></title>
        <link>https://archiejudd.com</link>
      </image>
      <atom:link href="https://archiejudd.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
      <language>en-us</language>
      <managingEditor>noreply@archiejudd.com (Archie Judd)</managingEditor>
      <webMaster>noreply@archiejudd.com (Archie Judd)</webMaster>
      <lastBuildDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 21:58:08 GMT</lastBuildDate>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
      <ttl>60</ttl>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[I'm going long on medium duration unhedged government bonds baby!]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[What follows is the inaugural annual investment ramble as part of my five year (likely longer [possibly shorter!]) plan to buy a house. This isn't advice, I don't know what I'm talking about, I am just organising my inexpert thoughts and I won't make a habit of it. US Equities are expensive The seven largest tech stocks of the SandP 500 make up 34.4% of its total market cap.]]></description>
      <link>https://archiejudd.com/posts/medium-duration-unhedged-bonds/</link>
      <guid>https://archiejudd.com/posts/medium-duration-unhedged-bonds/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[I saw an octopus, briefly]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[I was looking at a small, unremarkable fish through my mask when, in front of it, I noticed a soft orange-y tube that was sticking out at a right-angle from a rock. After some seconds I realised the tube was dilating and the rock had eyes, which were looking at me. I pointed at it and it started to rise up, slowly, as if bracing for a dash. It kept its tentacles hidden to maintain plausible deniability. I surfaced to tell my girlfriend. She thought I was pointing at the small fish.]]></description>
      <link>https://archiejudd.com/posts/i-saw-an-octopus/</link>
      <guid>https://archiejudd.com/posts/i-saw-an-octopus/</guid>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Aug 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title><![CDATA[Kiefer / Van Gogh at the Royal Academy]]></title>
      <description><![CDATA[The exhibition is at the back of the RA, in 3 rooms. Each room has one or two enormous Kiefer canvasses, and a handful of his smaller works. There are a few Van Goghs, but they feel like they're there to provide context rather than take the spotlight. The contrast between the two is stark. Kiefer's canvasses are imposing, textured, and opulent; Van Gogh’s are much more subdued. Both carry a sense of solitude, and capture the mystical quality of the landscapes they depict.]]></description>
      <link>https://archiejudd.com/posts/kiefer-van-gogh/</link>
      <guid>https://archiejudd.com/posts/kiefer-van-gogh/</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    </channel>
  </rss>